William Mansfield Clark Papers 1903-1964 Mss.B.C547
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1903-1964; 3.5 lin. feet
  Johns Hopkins University Medical School
  Journal of Biological Chemistry
  La Mer, Victor K.
  Lea & Febiger Publishers
  Lubs, Herbert A.
  Luck, J. Murray
  Michaelis, Leonor
  National Academy of Sciences
  National Academy of Sciences, Advisory
  Committee on Biological Warfare
  National Research Council
  Park, Edwards A.
  Richards, A. N.
  Rodkey, F. Lee
  Society of American Bacteriologists
  United States Department of Agriculture
  United States Public Health Service
  Van Slyke, Donald D.
  Vickery, Hubert B.
  Warburg, Otto
  Weed, Lewis H.
  Williams College
  Williams & Wilkins Company
  Winslow, C. -E. A.
  Woods, Alan C.
  - Abel, John J. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Medical School
  - Abel, Robert, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Abelson, Philip H. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Science
  - Abbott Laboratories (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, NRC Antimalarial Drug Program
  - Academic Press, Inc., 1955-1958 (Box 1)
  - Acree, S. F., 1939 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Elijah, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Adams, Ralph N., n.d. (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, NRC Antimalarial Drug Program
  - Adams, Roger, 1945 (Box 1)
  - Adkins, Homer (Box 1)
  - Advisory Commission of the Council of National Defense (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, NRC
  - Alberty, Robert A., 1953 (Box 1)
  - Albritton, Errett C. (Box 1)
  - Allen, A. J., 1945 (Box 1)
  - Alsberg, Carl L.Agriculture (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, US Department of
  - Ambler, Joseph A.Agriculture (Box 1)
  - The American Academy of Microbiology, 1957 (Box 1)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1959 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, Journal of Biological Chemistry
    -see also Ser. I, Science
    -see also Ser. II, AAAS
  - American Chemical Society (ACS), 1920-1954, n.d. (Box 1)
    Baldwin, Robert T.
    Johnston, John
    Montgomery, Jack P.
    Murray, Thomas F., Jr.
    Noyes, William A.
    Parsons, Charles L.
    -see also Ser. II, ACS
  - ACS Chemical Abstracts Service, 1963 (Box 1)
  - ACS New York Section. William H. Nichols Medal, 1935-1936; 3 folders (Box 1)
    Bayne-Jones, S.
    Bowman, Isaiah
    Breed, Robert S.
    Chemical Society of Washington
    Drabkin, David L.
    Grady, James T.
    Hixson, A. W.
    Lubs, H. A.
    Morgan, D. P.
    Rogers, L. A.
    Rose, William C.
    -see also Ser. II, ACS New York Section. William H.Nichols Medal
    -see also Ser. IV, "A Little Perspective of Acid-Base and Oxidation-Reduction Equilibria"
    -see also Ser. V, [Hastings, A. Baird] "The Scientific Career and Achievements of William Mansfield Clark..."
    -see also Ser. V, [Van Slyke, Donald D.] "Notes on the Personal Career of William Mansfield Clark..."
  - American Cyanamid Company (Box 1)
  - American Heart Association (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Chinard, Francis P.
  - American Insititute of Electrical Engineers, 1955, 1961 (Box 1)
  - American Men of Science, 1948 (Box 1)
  - American Physiological Society. Handbook of Physiology, 1961 (Box 1)
    Brown, David H.
    Cori, Carl F.
    Cori, Gerty T.
  - American Public Health Association (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Cohen, Barnett
  - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1931-1957 (Box 1)
    Handler, Philip
    King, C. G.
    Shaffer, Philip A.
    Wilson, D. Wright
    -see also Ser. I, NRC. Office of Critical Tables
    -see also Ser. II, American Society of Biological Chemists
    -see also Ser. IV, "Report of the Representative..."
  - American Zinc & Chemical Co., 1923 (Box 1)
  - American Zinc, Lead and Smelting Co., 1923 (Box 1)
  - Ames, Joseph [S.] (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I., JHU
  - Analytical Chemistry, 1957 (Box 1)
    Hallett, L. T.
    Nightingale,
  - Anderson, Rudolph J. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Journal of Biological Chemistry
    -see Ser. I, ACS New York Section. William H. Nichols Medal
  - Andrus, E. Cowles (Box 1)
  - Annual Review of Biochemistry, 1960-1962 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. IV, "Notes on a Half-Century of Research, Teaching, and Administration"
  - Archibald, R. M. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, JHU
  - Archives of Biochemistry and Biophysics, 1957 (Box 1)
    Gold, Victor
    -see also Ser. IV, pH Measurements. Their Theory and Practice, by Victor Gold--Review
  - Argonne National Laboratory, 1953-1954 (Box 1)
    Tahmisian, T. N.
  - Arons, Arnold B., 1955 (Box 1)
  - Ashley-Ratcliff Corp. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Walter J. Johnson, Inc.
  - Austrian, Charles R., [1948 or 1952] (Box 1)
  - Bacteriological Reviews, 1952, 1955 (Box 1)
    Gest, Howard
    Wilson, Perry W.
  - Baetjer, Howard, II (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, The Williams & Wilkins Company
  - Baker, Ber[itia] (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Baker, Robert
  - Baker, Henry S. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Treasurer
  - Baker, Lillian (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, La Mer, Victor K.
  - Baker, Robert, 1952 (Box 1)
    Baker, Ber[itia]
    Huggins, Charles
    Landmann, Paul E.
  - Baldwin, I. L. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. II, "Barnett Cohen, 1891-1952: An Appreciation"
  - Ball, Eric G., 1937-1963 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, Cohen, Barnett
    -see also Ser. II, "Notes on a Half-Century..."
    -see also Ser. II, Oxidation-Reduction Potentials of Organic Systems
    -see also Ser. I, Quarterly Review of Biology
    -see also Ser. I, Rodkey, F. Lee
  - Ballentine, Robert, 1961 (Box 1)
  - Baltimore (Md.) Board of Estimates, 1949 (Box 1)
  - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Willard, Daniel
  - Bang, Frederick B. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Bulletin of the Johns Hopkins Hospital
  - Barbaudy, Jean, 1927 (Box 1)
    In French
  - Bard, Phil[ip], 1950, 1953 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, JHU Herter Lectureship Committee
    -see also Ser. I, NRC
  - Barnes, Frederick W., Jr., 1948, 1951 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, Johns Hopkins Hospital
  - Barron, E. S. Guzman, 1947, 1954 (Box 1)
  - Bartlett, Paul D., 1953 (Box 1)
  - Bass, L. W. (Box 1)
  - Bates, Roger G., 1950-1963, n.d. (Box 1)
    Filley, Giles F.
    -see also Ser. IV, Electrometric pH Determinations...
  - Battegay, Martin (Box 1)
  - Baumberger, J. Percy, 1948, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Baxter, James P., 3rd. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Williams College
  - Bayliss, John R., 1922 (Box 1)
  - Bayliss, W. M., 1920 (Box 1)
  - Bayne-Jones, S., 1923-1929, n.d. (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, ACS New York Section. William H. Nichols Medal
    -see also Ser. I, The Society of American Bacteriologists
    -see also Ser. VI, Galvanometer
  - Beadle, George W.Medicine (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Nobel Committee.
  - Beetlestone, Mary (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Bryn Mawr College
  - Benedict, Stanley R. (Box 1)
  - B[enton], Anne (Box 1)
    -see Ser. II, "Evolution Toward a Mature Scientific Literature"
  - Benton, William, 1950 (Box 1)
  - Berry, George Packer, 1952 (Box 1)
    Rosenberg, Mollie Cohen
    Scherp, Henry W.
    -see also Ser. II, "Barnett Cohen, 1891-1952: An Appreciation"
  - Berthelot, Albert, 1926 (Box 1)
    Some in French
  - Bethlehem-Fairfield Shipyard, Inc., 1945 (Box 1)
  - Bhatnagar, G. M., 1960 (Box 1)
  - Biochemical Preparations, 1946-1963 (Box 1)
    Carter, H. E.
    Vestling, Carl S.
  - Biochemist's Handbook, 1957 (Box 1)
    Long, Cyril
  - Biodynamica Monographs, 1953 (Box 1)
  - Biological Abstracts, 1936 (Box 1)
    Schramm, J. R.
  - Bishop, E. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Indicators
  - Blalock, Alfred, 1948 (Box 1)
  - Blanchard, Kenneth Clark, 1948 (Box 1)
    US Civil Service Commission
  - Blum, [W?] (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, US Department of Commerce
  - Board for the Coordination of Malaria Studies (Box 1)
  - Bogert, Marston T. (Box 1)
  - Boland, V. J. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Lea & Febiger Publishers
  - Bonney, Lillian Powell, 1940-1952, n.d. (Box 1)
  - The Bonney Concert Bureau (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Bonney, Lillian Powell
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 1)
    -see Ser. II, Bowman, Isaiah
  - Breed, Robert S., 1929 (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, ACS. New York Section. William H. Nichols Medal
  - Brickwedde, F. G., 1946 (Box 1)
  - Brinkhous, K. M. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, Irvin, J. Logan
  - British Standards Institution, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Brode, 1928 (Box 1)
  - Broh-Kahn, R. H., 1948 (Box 1)
  - Bronk, Detlev, 1948-1952, n.d. (Box 1)
    -see also Ser. I, JHU
    -see also Ser. I, JHU. Committee on the Chemistry Department
    -see also Ser. I, NAS
    -see also Ser. I, NRC Office of Critical Tables
    -see also Ser. I, Warburg, Otto
  - Brook, M. M. (Box 1)
  - Brooks, Matilda M., 1953 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Claude P. (Box 1)
  - Brown, David H. (Box 1)
    -see Ser. I, American Physiological Society. Handbook of Physiology
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1955 (Box 1)
    Beetlestone, Mary
    Glenn, Nataliex
  - Buchanan, R. E. (Box 2)
  - Bucher, Gorden E. (Box 2)
  - Bucherer, H. T. (Box 2)
  - Buck, John B., 1949 (Box 2)
  - Buckner, H. G. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, The Hotchkiss School
  - Buehler, Reginal., 1953 (Box 2)
    Shryock, Richard H.
  - Bulletin of the Johns Hopkins Hospital, 1949 (Box 2)
  - Burford, William B., III, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
  - Burgan, H. C. (Box 2)
  - Burton, Kenneth, 1953, 1958 (Box 2)
  - Bush, Vannevar (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, National Resources Planning Board
    -see Ser. I, Office of Scientific Research and Development
  - Cambridge Instrument Company, Inc., 1954 (Box 2)
  - Campbell, Edward D. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Lilly Research Laboratories
  - Campbell Soup Company, 1953 (Box 2)
    -Kohman, E. F.
  - Cannan, R. Keith, 1924-1931, 1955, n.d. (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, Ball, Eric G.
    -see also Ser. V, [Cannan, R. Keith.] "Studies on Ectoplasm..."
  - Cannon, Walter B., 1928, 1937 (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, NAS
  - Caraway, Wendell T., 1950, 1956 (Box 2)
    Hearon, John Z.
    -see also Ser. V, Caraway, Wendell T. "The Use of a Mediator in Determining the Oxidation-Reduction Potentials of Sulfhydryl Compounds"
  - Carden, George A., Jr., 1945-1946, n.y. Aug. 5 (Box 2)
  - Carleton, P. W. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Company
  - Carmichael, Leonard (Box 2)
  - Carnes, William H. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Rosenberg, Lawson L.
  - Carter, Albert S. (Box 2)
  - Carter, H[erbert] E., 1952 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, Biochemical Preparations
  - Cassidy, Harold G., 1953 (Box 2)
  - Centro di Studio per la Polarografia, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Chambers, Robert (Box 2)
  - Chance, Britton, 1952, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Chase, George L., 1948 (Box 2)
    Refers to WMC as "Uncle Bill"
  - Chemical Abstracts, 1957, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, 1950, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Chemical Reviews, 1960 (Box 2)
  - Chemical Society of Washington (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, ACS New York Section. William H.Nichols Medal
  - Chen, K. K., 1945 (Box 2)
  - Chen, Tung-Tou, 1950 (Box 2)
    Student of WMC
  - Chesney, Alan M. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Medical School, Committees
    -see Ser. II, "Notes on a Half-Century..."
  - Chinard, Francis P., 1953-1963, n.d. (Box 2)
    American Heart Association
    Guggenheim Memorial Foundation
    H., L.
    Haines, Samuel F.
    Loeb, Robert F.
    Mayo Clinic
    NRC Fellowship in Medical Sciences
    -see also Ser. I, Johns Hopkins Medical Society
    -see also Ser. I, JHU Medical School, Committees
    -see also Ser. II, Chinard, Francis P.
  - Clark, Anna Mansfield, [1938] (Box 2)
    WMC's sister
    Hall, Robert Foote
    -see also Ser. II, Clark, Anna Mansfield
    -see also Ser. II, Trinity Military Institute
  - Clark, Caroline S[coville Hopson], 1909, 1919-1921 (Box 2)
    WMC's mother
  - Clark, George L. (Box 2)
  - Clark, Harriet Allen (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Gladding, Harriet (Clark)
  - Clark, Margaret (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Sumner, Margaret (Clark)
  - Clark, Miriam G[oddard], 1964, n.d. (Box 2)
    "Mimi"
    Encyclopedia of American Biography
    Hellerman, Leslie
    National Cyclopedia of American Biography
    Vickery, H. B.
  - Clark, Paul F., 1953 (Box 2)
  - Clarke, Hans T., 1946, 1952 (Box 2)
  - Clarke, William L.-1935" (Box 2)
    -see Ser. II, "Biographical Memoir of Walter (Jennings) Jones, 1865
  - Cloos, Ernst (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Committee on the Chemistry Department
  - Cohen, Aaron (Box 2)
  - Cohen, Barnett (Box 2)
    American Public Health Association
    Battegay, Martin
    Brook, M. M.
    Bucherer, H. T.
    Burgan, Harry C.
    Chesney, Alan M.
    Clark, George L.
    Cole, Kenneth C.
    Cumming, Hugh S.
    Elvove, Elias
    Esgate, Edith
    Goldstein, Henri
    Greenstein, Jesse P.
    Holmes, W. C.
    [H]olthoff, N. W.
    Irwin, Marian
    Jacobs, M. H.
    [K]err, J. D.
    [Kirby, George H.], "Nick"
    Lansdale, Florence
    Major, Randolph T.
    Merck & Co., Inc.
    National Aniline & Chemical Co.
    NRC
    Parkinson, N. A.
    Phillips, Max
    Ponder, Eric
    Richardson, G. M.
    Smith, Lee Irvin
    US Department of Agriculture
    US Public Health Service
    Wrede, Fritz
    -see also Ser. I, Acree, S. F.
    -see also Ser. I, Berry, George Packer
    -see also Ser. I, JHU Medical School, Herter Lectureship Committee
    -see also Ser. I, Nyburg, Sidney L.
    -see also Ser. II, Cohen, Barnett
    -see also Ser. III, Cohen, Barnett. "Data on Dyes"
    -see also Ser. IV, "Barnett Cohen, 1891-1952: An Appreciation"
    -see also Ser. IV, "Barnett Cohen, 1891-1952: Remarks..."
    -see also Ser. VI, Cohen, Barnett
    - Folder 1, [1913]-30 (Box 2)
    - Folder 2, 1931-52 (Box 2)
  - Cohn, [Edwin J.] (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, The Passano Foundation, Inc.
    -see Ser. II, Passano Award
  - Cole, Kenneth C. (Box 2)
  - The Coleman & Bell Company, 1922 (Box 2)
  - Colowick, [Sidney L.], 1954 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, International Union of Biochemistry. Commission on Enzymes
  - Colston, J. A. Campbell, 1940-1941, 1952 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, Hamburger, Louis P.
  - Columbia University, 1949, 1954 (Box 2)
    Kirk, Grayson
    Thomas, Martha Reynolds
  - Columbia University Press, 1927 (Box 2)
  - The Comet, 1943 (Box 2)
  - Comité Du Cinquantenaire De La Mort De Pasteur (Box 2)
    -see Ser. II, Cinquantenaire De La Mort De Pasteur
  - Community Service, Inc. (Lakeville, Conn.), 1952 (Box 2)
  - Conant, James B., 1923, 1926, 1930, 1941 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, National Defense Research Committee
  - [Connet, H.], 1920 (Box 2)
  - Cooper, W. Clark (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, US Public Health Service
  - Cope, Freeman W., 1954 (Box 2)
  - Copenhagen, W. J., 1921 (Box 2)
  - Cori, Carl F., 1948, 1961 (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Cori, Gerty T.
  - Cori, Gerty T., 1948 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, American Physiological Society. Handbook of Physiology
  - Corless, Grace Grimmel, 1952-1953, n.d. (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, JHU Treasurer
  - Cornell University Medical College, 1937 (Box 2)
    re: postition offered WMC
    Ladd, William S.
    Neill, James
    Stockard, C. R.
  - Corner, George Washington, 1952, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Corning Glass Works, 1951, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
    Curtiss, William Hanford
  - Cosmos Club, 1937, n.d. (Box 2)
  - Cotzias, George C. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Metal Coordination in the Medical Sciences
  - Cowgill, Robert W., 1951-1962 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. II, Cowgill, Robert
    -see also Ser. V, Cowgill, Robert W. "An Introductory Survey of the Influence of pH on the Lysis of Red Cells by Pneumococcal Hemolysin" -- Manuscript
  - Cox, Henry L. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Steglitz, Julius
  - Cox, R. T. (Box 2)
  - Coy, Edward G., 1903 (Box 2)
  - Cromwell, Norman H. (Box 2)
  - Crosby, Edwin L. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Medical School, Herter Lectureship Committee
  - Cullen, Glenn E. (Box 2)
  - Cullen, Thomas S., 1938 (Box 2)
  - Cumming, Hugh S. (Box 2)
  - Curtiss, William Hanford, 1951, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Corning Glass Works
  - Cushing, (Adm.) [H.] (Box 2)
  - Cuthbert, (Rev.) John S. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Sumner, Margaret Clark
  - Czerlinski, Georg, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Dahlberg, A. O. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Golden State Sales Corp.
  - Dandy, Walter E., Jr. (Box 2)
  - Daniels, F. E. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Pennsylvania. Department of Health
  - Daveron, Solon Alexander, 1931 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. VI, Daveron, Solon Alexander
  - Davis, Clark E. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, National Biscuit Company
  - Dawes, E. A., 1955 (Box 2)
  - Deane, Norman, 1956 (Box 2)
  - De Camp, John A. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Williamstown Massachusetts Public Schools
  - Decker, P. W., 1950 (Box 2)
  - De Haiek, Maria Esther Slafer, 1954 (Box 2)
  - de Kruif, Paul (Box 2)
  - Dent, J. N. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, University of Virginia. Medical School
  - Dernby, K. G., 1919-1923 (Box 2)
  - Dieke, G. H. (Box 2)
  - Dierson, Frank T., 1944 (Box 2)
  - Dieuaide, (Lt. Col.) Francis R., 1945 (Box 2)
  - Dimler, Fred J. (Box 2)
  - Doan, (Col.) H. W. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, US War Department
  - Dochez, A. R., 1944 (Box 2)
  - Doisy, E. A., 1952 (Box 2)
  - Donnan, F. G., 1923 (Box 2)
  - Doriot, (Gen.) Georges F. (Box 2)
  - Drabkin, David L., 1948 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. VI, [JHU Medical School], Laboratory Interiors
  - Dubos, René J. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, The Society of American Bacteriologists
  - Dunning, H. A. Brown (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Hynson, Westcott & Dunning
  - Dunning, J. H. Fitzgerald (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, JHU Alumni Association
  - E. I. du Pont de Nemours & Company, 1932, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
    Carleton, P. W.
    Carter, Albert S.
    Tinker, J. M.
  - E. P. Dutton and Company, 1961 (Box 2)
  - du Vigneaud, Vincent, 1958 (Box 2)
    -see also Ser. I, American Society of Biological Chemists
  - Dwek, Joseph (Box 2)
  - Earle, C. A. (Box 2)
  - Edsall, John T. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, NRC Office of Critical Tables
  - Ehrensvärd, Gösta (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, John Wiley & Sons, Inc.
  - Eisenhart, L. P. (Box 2)
  - Eisenhower, [Milton S.] (Box 2)
  - Elderfield, Robert C. (Box 2)
  - Elema, B., 1958-1959 (Box 2)
  - Elkridge Club (Baltimore, Md.), 1955-56 (Box 2)
  - Elvehjem, Conrad A. (Box 2)
  - Elvove, Elias (Box 2)
  - Emmet (Box 2)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1951-1952 (Box 2)
  - Encyclopedia of American Biography (Box 2)
    -see Ser. I, Clark, Miriam G[oddard]
  - Enders, Howard E. (Box 2)
    -see Ser. II, "Biographical Memoir of Walter (Jennings) Jones, 1865-1935"
  - Eppley, Marion, 1921 (Box 3)
  - Ernst, Morris L., 1961 (Box 3)
  - Esgate, Edith (Box 3)
  - Estill, Joe Garner, 1940 (Box 3)
  - Evans, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Fales, Harold A., 1920 (Box 3)
  - Falk, I. S. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Jordan, Edwin O.
  - Falk, J. E., 1953 (Box 3)
  - Fattovich, Giovanni, 1948 (Box 3)
  - The Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, 1933 (Box 3)
    Miller, C. Phillip
    -see also Ser. IV, "Discussion of [Philip A.] Shaffer's Paper"
  - Fellers, C. R. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, US Department of Agriculture
  - Fenn, Wallace O., 1928 (Box 3)
  - Fenwick, Florence, 1927 (Box 3)
  - Ferreira, Ricardo, 1963 (Box 3)
  - Ferry, Frederick C. (Box 3)
  - Filley, Giles F., 1953, 1963 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, Bates, Roger G.
  - Fippin, E. O. (Box 3)
    -see National Lime Association
  - Fi[scher, N.?], 1929 (Box 3)
    in German
  - Fisher, Harry L. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, International Congress of Pure and Applied Chemistry (12th)
  - Flynn, [ca. 1953] (Box 3)
  - Folkers, Karl, 1959 (Box 3)
  - Foote Mineral Company, Inc., 1923 (Box 3)
    Meyer, H. C.
  - Forrestal, James (Box 3)
  - Foster, E. M. (Box 3)
  - Fountain, H. Howard, 1925 (Box 3)
  - Fowle (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Meyer, Adolf
  - Fowler, George A., 1952 (Box 3)
  - Fowler, Robert D. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I. Chemical and Engineering News
  - Fraser, Charles G., 1948 (Box 3)
  - Fred, E. B., 1934, 1945 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, The American Society of Bacteriologists
  - French Embassy (Box 3)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas S., 1952-1953, n.d. (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, JHU Medical School
    -see also Ser. V, Friedenwald,
    Jonas S. "Elementary Theory of Enzymatic Activity..."
  - Friedman, Meyer, 1941 (Box 3)
  - Frost, W. H. (Box 3)
  - Fruton, Joseph S., 1952-1959 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, Harbury, Henry
  - Fucoma Company, Inc., 1929 (Box 3)
  - Fuller, Henry R. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Houghton Mifflin Company
  - Funk, F. J., 1924 (Box 3)
  - Gaebler, O. H., 1952 (Box 3)
  - Gallagher, T. F., 1949 (Box 3)
  - [Gamble], J. L., 1945, n.d. (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. IV, Chemical Anatomy, Physiology...
  - Gammon, Edgar G. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Hampden-Sydney College
  - Garland, Charles S. (Box 3)
  - Gas Rationing Board, 1942, 1944 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. II, Gas Rationing Board
  - Gasser, Herbert, 1942, 1944, 1955 (Box 3)
  - J. Norman Geipe Van Lines, Inc., 1952 (Box 3)
  - Gemmill, Chalmers L., 1948 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, University of Virginia. Medical School
  - Gentzkow, C. J., 1943, 1951-1956 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, Lea & Febiger Publishers
    -see also Ser. I, Simmons, (Col.) James S.
    -see also Ser. IV, "Hydrogen Ion Determinations..."
  - George, Philip, 1961 (Box 3)
    Gryder, John
  - Gest, Howard (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Bacteriological Reviews
  - Gibbs, John S., Jr. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Johns Hopkins Hospital
  - Gilbert, Judson B., 1938 (Box 3)
  - Gill, Robert S. (Box 3)
  - Gillespie, L. J., 1920-1926, 1939 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. II, Gillespie, L. J.
  - Gilman, Henry (Box 3)
  - Gladding, Harriet (Clark), 1925, 1949 (Box 3)
    WMC's daughter
    -see also Ser. II, "Notes on a Half-Century of Research, Teaching and Administration"
  - Glass, H. Bentley (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Quarterly Review of Biology
  - Glenn, Natalie (Box 3)
  - Goddard, C. Allen, 1927, 1943, 1946 (Box 3)
    WMC's father-in-law
  - Goddard, Eunice R., 1947 (Box 3)
  - [Goddard?], Lindley, 1956 (Box 3)
  - Gold, Victor (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Archives of Biochemistry and Biophysics
    -see Ser. IV, pH Measurements: Their Theory and Practice
  - Golden State Sales Corporation, 1926 (Box 3)
    Dahlberg, A. O.
  - Goldstein, Henri (Box 3)
  - Grady, James T. (Box 3)
  - Grafflin, Allan L., 1950 (Box 3)
    Ochoa, Severo
    -see also Ser. I, JHU School of Medicine, Herter Lectureship Committee
  - Green, David E., 1959 (Box 3)
  - Greenstein, Jesse P. (Box 3)
  - Grimmel, Grace (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Corless, Grace Grimmel
  - Grose, William E., 1960, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Gross, Paul (Box 3)
  - Gryder, John (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, George, Philip
    -see Ser. III, "[John] Gryder's Theory"...
    -see Ser. III, "... [John] Gryder's System"
  - Guggenheim, Paul, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Fellowships (Box 3)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Box 3)
  - Gunsalus, Irwin, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Guttmacher, Dorothy E. (Box 3)
  - Haines, Samuel F. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I., Chinard, Francis P.
  - Hall, Robert Foote, 1938 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, Clark, Anna
    -see also Ser. II, Trinity Military
    Institute
  - Halla, Roman J., 1949 (Box 3)
  - Hallett, L. T. (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, Analytical Chemistry
  - Hamburger, Louis P., 1940 (Box 3)
    -see also Ser. I, Colston, J. A. Campbell
  - Hamilton Street Club, 1942 (Box 3)
  - Hampden-Sydney College, 1952 (Box 3)
    Gammon, Edgar G.
  - Handbook of Biological Data (Box 3)
  - Handler, Philip (Box 3)
    -see Ser. I, American Society of Biological Chemists
  - Harbury, Henry, 1952-1963 (Box 3)
    WMC student
    JHU
    Lilly Research Grants Committee
    Research Corporation
    Winzler, Richard
    -see also Ser. I, Chance, Britton
    -see also Ser. I, Fruton, Joseph S.
    -see also Ser. I, Theorell, Hugo
    -see also Ser. I, University of California (Berkeley). Virus Laboratory
    -see also Ser. II, Harbury, Henry
    -see also Ser. III, Harbury, Henry and Paul A. Loach...
  - Harding, T. Swann (Box 3)
  - Hardy, F., 1926-1927 (Box 3)
  - Harper, J. E. (Box 3)
  - Harris, Joseph, 1953-1962 (Box 3)
    Roseman, Saul
  - Harrison, Ross G. (Box 3)